

Rizki Nugroho

As a Web and Mobile Developer with more than 1 year of experience. Is passionate and experienced in developing mobile applications. Mastered various programming languages and frameworks. Have great problem solving and critical thinking.

Tangerang 📈 rizkinhg@gmail.com / 081586261393 😱 rizkinugroho.netlify.app



Experience

Project-Based Virtual Intern: Mobile Apps Developer - Bank Mandiri x Rakamin Academy

PT Bank Mandiri (Persero) Tbk.

Complete various tasks related to Mobile Apps Developer from Bank Mandiri such as:

- 1. Android: Environment & Lifecycle, UI and Design Pattern, RecyclerView, and Database.
- 2. Kotlin: XML, Gradle, Principles of Kotlin, and OOP.
- 3. iOS: Swift, XCode Mastery, UI in iOS, Collections and Localization, and Data Persistence and Web Services.
- 4. Unit Testing: Principles of Unit Testing, Unit Testing Tools, Unit Testing Instrument.
- 5. Gitlab: Principles of Gitlab, Operation, and Features of Gitlab.
- 6. API (Aplication Programing Interface): Principles of API, Basic Operation of API, Restful API.

September 2023 - October 2023

Data Warehouse Administrator • PT DutaFlow Hidrolik

Responsible for:

- 1. Develop and create schedules for the data warehouse.
- 2. Design, develop, and maintain a data warehouse.

November 2021 - August 2023

Freelance Web Developer · Upwork

As a web developer I am responsible:

- Develop dan maintenance web applications sistem
- Technology used: Node JS, React JS, MongoDB, Bootstrap, Figma

April 2022 - August 2023

Education

Jan 2022 - Now

Universitas Insan Pembangunan Indonesia sistem informasi

Skill

- Programming: Javascript, Java, Php
- Mobile Developer: Kotlin, Flutter, React Native
- Web Developer: Node Js, React Js, Laravel, Restful Api
- Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Tools : Android Studio, Visual Studio, Intellij IDEA

Certificate

- Back End Development and APIs Freecodecamp.org
- Build Application with Kotlin Dicoding Indonesia
- Build Web Service With Node Js Dicoding Indonesia
- Responsive Web Design Freecodecamp.org
- Junior Web Developer Digitalent Kominfo